iranian.com 2015-06-13

# Iranian.com - Iran News, Blogs and Community

## Iranian.com Privacy Policy

**Our Privacy Policy and Use of Your Information**

Iranian.com, through itself and its subsidiaries (“Iranian.com” or “we”) created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your personal information and informing you on how it is handled. This Privacy Policy only applies to transactions and activities in which you engage and data gathered on Iranian.com (the “Site”). It does not apply to any other website or offline point of contact between Iranian.com, or any other company, site, or consumers. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time. Each time you visit the Site or provide Iranian.com with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time.

We hope that you will want to provide some information about yourself to Iranian.com by becoming a “registered user,” because it will make your experience here more valuable to you and to other members of the community. If you are comfortable sharing some basic information about yourself, you will receive enhanced services that are otherwise not possible to offer to unregistered users.

Regardless, this Privacy Policy applies to all “users,” whether registered or not. However you choose to interact with Iranian.com, you have our pledge that we will manage your privacy information in accordance with the policies set forth herein. Please note that we may share information about you to respond to subpoenas, search warrants, judicial proceedings, court orders, legal process, or other law enforcement measures, to establish or exercise our legal rights, or to defend against legal claims.

If you choose to engage in public activities on the site, such as posting blogs/comments on the site, any information you submit can be read, collected, or used by others. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information in public activities or submissions. Please also remember that Iranian.com is not targeted to children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.

We may share information about you in the event that the Site is acquired by or merged with another company or a similar corporate transaction takes place. However, the Site will notify you by placing a prominent notice on our site or sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account before your information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. We may also share information about you to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety or other rights and interests of any person, violations of the Site's Terms and Conditions, or as otherwise required by law.

**When you visit Iranian.com ("cookies")**

Cookies are used on the Iranian.com Web site to manage advertising banner displays by our advertising partners. Iranian.com cookies from registered users also may contain a user's username(s) so that the username is “remembered” on the computer. We use Google Adsense and other advertising networks, and they have their own cookies, for which we are not responsible. Google uses the DoubleClick DART cookie/AdJuggler, which enables it to serve you ads based on your visits to all sites on the Internet which support that cookie. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information.

We also gather traffic patterns and Site usage information, such as browser type, referring URL, and IP address, in order to help us develop the design and layout of the Site. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information about you.

We have relationships with advertisers and vendors who sell products and services to customers who click from Iranian.com to the vendor's Web site. We may use broad demographic or geographic information provided by you to target ads, but no advertiser will have access to your personally identifying information. In cases where you click through to an advertisers’ site, Iranian.com does not collect any information about you, and any information provided by you to these vendors and service providers would fall under the privacy policy of such vendor(s). These are external to the Iranian.com Web site, and therefore not under the control of Iranian.com.

We may also share aggregate statistical information regarding our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and Site usage with our commercial partners. For example, we may develop summary, not individual, reports for our advertisers or sponsors. An example of a summary report might be "800 people clicked on Advertisement Z today."

We also may use this general information in conjunction with generally available marketing databases so that we better understand our customers and can tailor our products, services and Content to meet our customers' needs and preferences. This information is for use by Iranian.com only and is not shared with third parties.

**Your IP Address**

Like most e-commerce Websites, each time you visit the Site, we automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. To administer and optimize the Site for you and to diagnose problems and issues with the Site, we may also use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you.

**When you register at Iranian.com**

In order to use some advanced features of Iranian.com, you must first complete the Site registration form. During registration, you must provide certain personal information (specifically “username”, first/last name and email address). We encourage, but do not require, that you use your real name as your username. We use this information to contact you about the Site's services in which you have expressed interest.

You have the option to provide certain demographic information, such as year of birth, “bio,” picture, personal Web site, social media identities, country of residence and gender. We encourage you to submit this information, so that we can provide a more personalized experience on the Site and as a benefit for our community of users. **Should you provide such demographic information, it will be displayed on your blog, and all Users can see it.** Note that your email address is NOT revealed or displayed. If you wish that certain demographic information not be displayed, please do not provide it. (If you have provided it and now wish that it not be displayed, simply “Edit Your Profile” page and remove the information.)

Registered users may also subscribe or unsubscribe for activity notifications/email newsletters or for occasional special offers from our advertisers. In both cases, we will not intentionally reveal your email address to advertisers or other users.

You may opt out of receiving any notifications by “unsubscribing” to these offers on your “Account Settings” page.

We use your email address to respond to questions you ask us or for certain administrative communications such as forgotten passwords or confirming activities on your account. And we may use your email address to send you email regarding the status of your user account.

**Deactivating Your Account**

You can deactivate your account at any time by visiting the “Account Settings” for your profile. When you deactivate your account, your user profile will be disabled, but your blogs and public comments will remain on the site. **The Site has no responsibility to take down, remove, or edit any of your public activities or any submissions that are a result of your public activities.** For more information, please review our Terms and Conditions.

**Public Forums**

Iranian.com may provide public forums for our visitors to read and share information with other individuals. Disclosing personally identifiable information online through comments, forums, message boards or other Content makes the information public information. Please be careful and use discretion when disclosing any information in such a public forum.

**Advertising and Links to Other Sites**

We may use your personally identifying information to target certain ads based on your geographic location and/or demographic profile (specifically age and gender). We will not reveal your information to the advertiser.

Iranian.com has arrangements with third parties and advertising networks who provide advertising banners or sponsored links. We do our best to only link to reliable Web sites. However, Iranian.com cannot control the activities of any third parties or ad networks with regard to the ads that appear on our Site or once an Iranian.com customer leaves the Iranian.com Web site. If you have questions about the privacy policies of such third parties, we suggest contacting them directly or visiting their Web sites to review their posted privacy policies.

**Third Party Services**

To customize your experience on the Site and to simplify the Site's registration process, we provide you with the opportunity to access or interact with third-party services, such as Facebook and Twitter. When you connect to the Site through these third-party services, we may share information about you with these third-party service providers and they may share data about you with us.

In addition, if you connect to a Facebook account, your experience on the Site may be personalized. For example, you may automatically see what stories are popular in your network, and what your friends are saying about particular stories.

Please note that you may disconnect third party accounts at any time. You may be able to modify your privacy settings directly with the third-party service. To modify your Facebook privacy settings, click here. To modify your Twitter privacy settings, click here. 

Please remember that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party services. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all third-party service providers.

**Contests, Promotions and Surveys**

From time to time, we and/or third parties may offer the opportunity to participate in contests, promotions and surveys. If such contests, promotions or surveys are operated by third parties, by electing to participate you consent to our providing your personal information to those third parties. Those third parties may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. You will need to contact those third parties to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. Additionally, you agree we may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such third parties in the same manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information you submit to us.

**Confidentiality and security**

We limit access to contact information about you to employees/volunteers or service providers who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We also have adopted commercially reasonable technical, physical, and administrative procedures to help protect information about you from loss, misuse, and alteration.

Please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We want you to feel confident using the Site, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. In the event of an inadvertent disclosure of personal information, including through “hacking” or other unauthorized use of the website, you consent to World Singles notifying you electronically, via the e-mail address you provide upon registration, as to any disclosures it is required to make under the law, or decides to make voluntarily. The law may allow you the right to have such disclosure of compromised personal information made via mail, and you expressly waive that right.

We may update this privacy policy at any time to reflect changes in our practices and service offerings. If we modify this privacy policy, we will update the "Effective Date" found at the bottom of this page.

If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact our privacy team at [info@iranian.com](mailto:info@iranian.com)

Effective Date: March 1, 2013
